Damilola Alabi

Frontend Developer React

Osun state, Nigeria 🔒

+2348140711202

Alabidamilolad@gmail.com

LinkedIn in

Linktr.ee/eminencex

An enthusiastic reactJS developer who is eager to contribute to team success through hard work, attention to detail and excellent organizational skills. With clear understanding of frontend web development and training in backend web development, I'm motivated to learn, grow and excel in the tech space. I am an innovative and a tech-savvy individual with 3 years of experience in website design and web development, a seasoned expert in markups such as HTML and CSS, frameworks and libraries such as ReactJS, NodeJS and ExpressJS as well as scripting languages like JavaScript and typescript

Skills

- Excellent Communication
- Fast learner
- JavaScript

- Typescript
- ReactJS
- NodeJS

- ExpressJs
- Redux
- Git

Experience

2021-08 - 2022-05

Freelance Web Developer / Fiverr

- Planned website development, converting mockups into useable web presence with HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- Applied emerging technologies to update and maintain site application
- Coded websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and ReactJS

2020-11 - 2022-04

Freelance Web Designer / Fiverr

- Provide front-end website development using WordPress, SquareSpace, Wix and other CMS platforms.
- Adhered to SEO best practices while designing sites.
- Engaged with client to plan and optimize site issues and queries.
- Oversaw technical issues and troubleshooting requests to resolve user problems

Education

DECEMBER 2019 - CURRENT

Mathematics / Obafemi Awolowo University

• Bachelor Of Science, Mathematics